<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='Services.xsl'?>
<servicestypes>

<service>
<name>Conferences</name>
<description>A conference is a meeting of people who "confer" about a topic. Conference types include: 
Conference hall, room where conferences are held.Convention (meeting), meeting of a, usually large, 
group of individuals and/or companies in a certain field.</description>
<price>25 Lakhs</price>
<people>600</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>Product Launch</name>
<description>A product launch is when a company decides to launch a new product in the market. 
Product launch can be of an existing product which is already in the market or it can be a completely
 new innovative product which the company has made. 
Product launch involves various steps which involves understanding customer needs, product design, 
testing of the product, marketing and advertising and ensuring that the product reaches out to all its 
audience. A successful product launch provides a sales momentum for the company.</description>
<price>45 Lakhs</price>
<people>800</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>Trade Shows</name>
<description>A trade show is an event held to bring together members of a particular industry to display,
 demonstrate, and discuss their latest products and services. Major trade shows usually take place in 
 convention centers in larger cities and last several days. Local trade shows may be held at a local arena
  or hotel and allow businesses in the area to connect with prospects.Since the purpose is to bring 
  together members of the trade – or industry – most trade shows, which may also be referred to as trade 
  fairs or expositions, only permit industry members to attend.</description>
<price>30 Lakhs</price>
<people>600</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>Networking Events</name>
<description>Networking comes in different forms. One of the most popular is a networking event. 
It can be a conference wherein you can connect with the attendees and even the keynote speakers. 
It can also be a professional association event that is organized by an industry organization.
A professional networking event covers a specific market, allowing you to network with other people
 within the industry. You can also hone your networking skills during a community event, which can be a
  summer fair or a fundraising activity.</description>
<price>20 Lakhs</price>
<people>800</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>VIP Events</name>
<description>Event Management of VIP events which are an important marketing tool to increase and to 
maintain the loyality of key customers. Every company and organization has someone they consider a VIP. 
These people are often honored with VIP events. These people could be:
The company’s top customer. In some cases, a top customer could represent up to 50 percent of a company’s 
business. For a non profit organization, a VIP could be the top donor.</description>
<price>40 Lakhs</price>
<people>200</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>Award Ceremonies</name>
<description>An awards ceremony is a type of ceremony where awards are given out. The ceremony may be 
arranged by a government organization, a society, a school, a trade association or even a company that 
specializes in running awards ceremonies. Typically a master of ceremonies presents award winners, speaks 
to the audience, entertains people, and generally keeps the ceremony moving.</description>
<price>20 Lakhs</price>
<people>400</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>Weddings</name>
<description>A wedding is a ceremony where two or more people are united in marriage. ... 
Most wedding ceremonies involve an exchange of marriage vows by a couple, presentation of a gift 
(offering, rings, symbolic item, flowers, money, dress), and a public proclamation of marriage by an 
authority figure or celebrant.</description>
<price>30 Lakhs</price>
<people>500</people>
</service>

<service>
<name>Birthdays</name>
<description>A birthday is a day when a person celebrates the anniversary of his or her birth. Birthdays 
are celebrated in numerous cultures, often with a gift, party, or rite of passage. The celebration of a 
birthday usually is thought to mark how old a person is.</description>
<price>10 Lakhs</price>
<people>400</people>
</service>

</servicestypes>